美国魔法部
AMERICAN MINISTRY OF MAGIC
纽约  1927年
NEW YORK, 1927
我想你会很高兴摆脱他的
You'll be glad to be rid of him, I expect.
我们更希望的是就把他关在这里
We'd be more than happy to keep him here in custody.
关六个月就够了
Six months are enough.
现在是他对他在欧洲的罪行负责的时候了
It's time for him to answer for his crimes in Europe.
皮克雷主席  斯皮尔曼先生
President Picquery, Mr. Spielman, sir.
已做好对囚犯的安全保护  可以出发了
Prisoner is secured and ready to travel.
我能看出来  你把所有能用的东西都用在了他身上了
You've thrown everything at him, I see.
这是必要的措施  他非常强大
It was necessary. He's extremely powerful.
我们已经给他换了三次警卫了  他似乎...很有影响力
We've had to change his guard three times, he's very... persuasive.
所以我们切除了他的舌头
So we removed his tongue.
格林德沃   格林德沃
Grindelwald! Grindelwald!
主席女士  全世界的法师都欠你一个大人情
The wizarding community worldwide owes you a great debt, Madam President.
别小看他
Do not underestimate him.
斯皮尔曼先生  我们发现了他藏起来的法杖
Mr. Spielman, we found his wand hidden away.
阿伯纳西
Abernathy?
我们还发现了这个
And we found this.
不再是那么能说会道了
No more silver tongue, hmm?
你已经加入了一个崇高的事业  我的朋友
You have joined a noble cause, my friend.
我知道  我知道  我知道  安东尼奥
I know. I know. I know, Antonio
那么弱小无助
So needy.
神奇动物：格林德沃之罪
中文由janelk翻译 英文由Subtitled by Clarity提供
FANTASTIC BEASTS: THE CRIMES OF GRINDELWALD Subtitled by Clarity.
英国魔法部
BRITISH MINISTRY OF MAGIC
三个月后
THREE MONTHS LATER
他们已经准备好见你了  纽特
They're ready for you, Newt.
莉塔…
Leta...
你在这里做什么
What are you doing here?
忒修斯认为如果我能成为魔法部的家人会很好
Theseus thought it would be good if I became part of the Ministry family.
他真的说了"魔法部的家人"吗
Did he actually say the words “Ministry family?
听起来像我哥哥
That sounds like my brother
忒修斯很失望你不能来吃晚饭
Theseus was disappointed you couldn't come to dinner.
从来都不接受我们的晚饭邀请
Any of the nights we've asked you.
嗯  我一直很忙
Well, I've been busy.
他是你哥哥  纽特
He's your brother, Newt.
他喜欢和你在一起
He likes spending time with you.
我也是
And so do I.
喂  你   进去  皮克
Oi, you! Hop in, Pick.
为什么古怪的生物那么喜欢你
Why do strange creatures love you so much?
-好吧,没有古怪的生物  -只有心胸狭隘的人
- Well, there are no strange creatures... - Only blinkered people!
你因为对普伦德加斯特说这样的话而被扣留了多久
How long did you get in detention for saying that to Prendergast?
你知道的  那段时间差不多有一个月吧
You know, I think it was a month that time.
我在他桌子下放了一枚粪便炸弹  这样我就能和你一起了  你还记得吗
And I set off a Dung bomb under his desk so I could join you, do you remember?
不  我真的不记得了
No, I actually don't remember that.
你好
Hello.
忒修斯  我们在说纽特要来我们家里吃晚饭
Theseus. We were just talking about Newt coming for dinner
真的   那么
Really? Well...
听着  在我们进去之前我
Look, before we go in there I
这是我第五次了  忒修斯  我知道形式的
It's my fifth attempt, Theseus. I know the form.
这会不会像以前那样了  这会..
This isn't going to be like the other times. This is...
只是试着尽量听取别人的意见  好吗
Just try and keep an open mind, will you?
-就接受一下别那么  -太自我
- And maybe a little less. - Like me?
又没有坏处  快点  我们进去吧
Well, it can't hurt. Come on. Let's go.
听证会开始了
Hearing commences...
你想结束你的国际旅行禁令  为什么
You want an end to the ban on your traveling internationally. Why?
因为我喜欢去国际旅行
Because I like to travel internationally.
你对上一次国际旅行的原因采取不合作和回避的态度
Subject uncooperative and evasive on reasons for last international trip.
那是一次实地考察
It was a field trip.
我在那是为我那本关于神奇的动物的书收集素材
So I was collecting material for my book on magical beasts
你差不多毁了半个纽约
You destroyed half of New York.
不  实际上你说的这两点与事实非常不符
No, that's actually factually incorrect on two counts
纽特
Newt!
斯卡曼德先生.
Mr. Scamander...
很明显你很受挫  坦白说  我们也是
it's clear you're frustrated and, frankly, so are we.
本着妥协的精神  我们想提出一个建议
In the spirit of compromise, we'd like to make a proposition.
什么提议
What kind of proposition?
委员会将同意在一定条件下解除你的旅行禁令
The committee will agree to lift your travel ban under one condition.
你加入魔法部
You join the Ministry.
尤其是加入你哥哥的部门
Specifically, your brother's department.
不
No.
我不喜欢的那样...
I-that isn't my kind of...
忒修斯是傲罗
Theseus is the Auror...
我想我还是把我的才能用到别处吧
I think my talents lie elsewhere.
斯卡曼德先生  法师和非法师
Mr. Scamander. The wizarding and non-wizarding
已经在着世界上和平发展有一个多世纪了
worlds have been at peace for over a century.
格林德沃希望看到和平被摧毁
Grindelwald wants to see that peace destroyed.
对我们群体的某些成员来说  他传达的信息非常有诱惑性
And for certain members of our community his message is very seductive.
很多纯正血统的法师认为这是他们与生俱来的统治权
Many pure-bloods believe it is their birthright to rule
不仅是我们的世界  还有非魔法世界
not only our world but the non-magic world as well.
他们视格林德沃为英雄
They see Grindelwald as their hero,
而格林德沃却看到了这个男孩
and Grindelwald sees this boy
把他作为实现他目的一种手段
as a means to make this all come true.
等等  你说的好像克雷登斯好像还存在一样
I'm sorry. You're talking about Credence as if he were still here.
他活下来了  纽特
He survived, Newt.
他还活着
He is still alive.
他几个月前离开了纽约
He left New York months ago.
他在欧洲的某个地方  确切地说  我们也不知道在那  但是.
He's somewhere in Europe. Where exactly, we don't know, but...
你想让我去找克雷登斯
And you want me to hunt Credence down?
去杀他
To kill him?
斯卡曼德还是老样子
Same old Scamander.
他在这里做什么
What's he doing here?
你太软弱了  不能胜任这份工作
Taking on the job you're too soft to do.
就这样吗
Is that it?
旅行证件被拒绝
Travel documentation denied.
纽特
Newt!
你认为我比你更喜欢格里姆森这个主意吗
You think I like the idea of Grimmson any more than you do?
听着  忒修斯  我不想听你那些是非的教训话
Listen, I don't want to hear how the ends justify the means, Theseus.
我觉得是时候该把你的头抬起来了 看看现实了
I think you're gonna have to pull your head out of the sand!
好吧  好吧  开始说吧  说我多么自私..不负责任..
Okay, right, here we go. What a selfish... irresponsible...
你知道的  在现阶段每个人
You know, the time is coming when everyone's
每个人都得选一边  即使是你
everyone's gonna have to pick a side. Even you.
我不做旁门左道的事
I don't do sides.
纽特
Newt.
来吧
C'mere.
他们在监视你
They are watching you.
好吧  先生们
Well, gentlemen.
我想这意味着我要接手这份工作了
I assume this means I have the job.
法国巴黎
PARIS, FRANCE
奇瑞
Chérie?
谁在那儿
Who's there?
在彻底清洗之后  这将是很舒适的
This will be suitable after a thorough cleanse.
我要你现在去马戏团
I want you to go to the circus now.
把我的信交给克雷登斯
Give my note to Credence,
让他启程
begin his journey.
一旦我们赢了  就会有数以百万计的人逃离城市
When we've won, they'll flee cities in the millions.
他们现在还有的是时间
They've had their time.
我们不会大声说出来的
We don't say such things out loud.
我们只想要自由
We want only freedom.
属于我们的自由
Freedom to be ourselves.
消灭非法师
To annihilate non-wizards.
不是所有的人  不是全部
Not all of them. Not all.
我们不是那么无情的
We're not merciless.
留下一些驮畜永远是必要的
The beast of burden will always be necessary.
[英国伦敦]
[London, UK]
Ventus.
邓布利多
Dumbledore.
那么  就不能找个不那么显眼的屋顶吗
Were the less conspicuous rooftops full, then?
我很喜欢看这里的风景
I do enjoy a view.
Nebulus.
怎么样
How was it?
他们仍然相信是你派我去纽约的
They're still convinced that you sent me to New York.
你告诉他们我没有
You told them I didn't?
对
Yes.
但事实是你送我去
Even though you did.
你告诉我在哪能找到那只被贩卖的雷鸟
You told me where to find that trafficked Thunderbird,
邓布利多  你知道我会带他回家
Dumbledore. You knew that I would take him home and you
而你知道我得带他穿过麻瓜港口
knew I'd have to take him through a Muggle port.
嗯  我一直觉得自己和神奇的大鸟很亲近
Well, I've always felt an affinity with the great magical birds..
我家里有个故事
There's a story in my family
凤凰会来到任何一个邓布利多家族成员最需要的它地方
that a phoenix will come to any Dumbledore who is in desperate need.
他们说我的曾曾祖父有一个  但是当他死的时候它飞走了
They say my great-great grandfather had one, but that it took flight when he died,
永不回头
never to return.
恕我直言  我一刻也不相信
With all due respect, I don't believe for a minute
所以你才告诉我雷鸟的事
that's why you told me about the Thunderbird.
克雷登斯在巴黎  纽特
Credence is in Paris, Newt.
他想追踪他真正的家人
He's trying to trace his real family.
知道了
I take it.
你听过谣言
You've heard the rumors
关于他到底是谁
about who he really is?
没有
No.
纯正血统的法师认为他是法国某个大家族的唯一后人
The pure-bloods think he's the last of an important French line,
一个被所有人认为丢失已久的孩子
a baby whom everyone thought lost
-不是莉塔的兄弟吗   -他们就是这么窃窃私语的
- Not Leta's brother? - That's what they're whispering.
不管是不是纯血统的  我知道这...
Pure-blood or not, I know this...
在没有关爱的情况下成长
An Obscurus grows in the absence of love
把黑暗当成唯一的朋友
as a dark twin, an only friend.
如果克雷登斯有一个真正的兄弟或姐妹或许可以取代默默然的位置
If Credence has a real brother or sister out there that can take its place,
他也许还能得救
he might yet be saved.
无论克雷登斯在巴黎的什么地方  他要么处于危险之中  要么对他人构成危险
Wherever Credence is in Paris, he's either in danger or a danger to others.
我们可能还不知道他是谁  但需要找到他
We may not know who he is yet, but he needs to be found.
我很希望你能找到他
And I rather hoped you might be the one to find him.
那是什么
What's that?
我一个老熟人的地址
An address of a very old acquaintance of mine.
巴黎的一座安全的房子  用魔法加固的
A safe house in Paris, reinforced with enchantments.
安全屋   为什么我要在巴黎要有个安全屋
Safe house? Why would I need a safe house in Paris?
希望你不会用上  但世事难料
One hopes you won't, but should things at some point
万一出了大错  有个地方可以去是件好事
go terribly wrong, it's good to have a place to go.
你知道的  也许还能喝一杯茶
You know, for a cup of tea.
不  不  不  绝对不行
No, no, no, absolutely not.
我被禁止国际旅行了  邓不利多
I'm banned from international travel, Dumbledore.
如果我离开这个国家  他们会把我关在阿兹卡班  然后扔掉钥匙的
If I leave the country, they will put me in Azkaban and throw away the key.
你知道我为什么那么欣赏你吗  纽特
Do you know why I admire you, Newt?
什么
What?
在我认识的人里面
More, perhaps, than any man I know?
你不追求权力和声望
You don't seek power or popularity.
你只需问  做这件事情是对的吗
You simply ask, is the thing right in itself?
如果是  你就会去做  不管付出多大代价
If it is, you do it, no matter the cost.
很好  邓布利多  但是  冒昧的问你一句
That's all very well, Dumbledore, but, forgive me for asking,
为什么你不能去
why can't you go?
我不能和格林德沃对着干
I cannot move against Grindelwald.
一定要是你
It has to be you.
好吧  我不怪你
Well, I can't blame you,
如果是我站在你的立场上  我也可能会拒绝
in your shoes I'd probably refuse too.
-什么...   -天色已晚
- What...? - It's late.
-晚安  纽特   -等等  不
- Good evening, Newt. - Wait. No!
哦  别这样
Oh, come on.
邓布利多
Dumbledore.
布蒂
Bunty!
布蒂  嗅嗅宝宝又跑出来了
Bunty, the baby Nifflers are loose again!
干得好
Well done
我很抱歉  纽特
I'm so sorry, Newt.
他们一定是在我清理奥格瑞的时候跑出来的
They must have picked the lock while I was cleaning out the Augureys
别担心
Not to worry.
我几乎给每个人都吃过了  给小粉用过了滴鼻剂
I've fed nearly everyone, Pinky's had his nose drops, and
还有埃尔茜呢
And Elsie?
-埃尔茜的粪便几乎又正常了   -太好了
- Elsie's droppings are nearly normal again. - Wonderful.
你现在可以下班了
You can clock off now...
-我告诉过你把马形水鬼留给我   -那个伤口需要更多的药膏
- I told you to leave the Kelpie to me. - That wound needs more ointment.
我不想让你失去手指
I don't want you losing fingers over it.
说真的  你现在回家去吧  布蒂
Seriously, you go home now, Bunty.
你一定累坏了
You must be exhausted.
你知道的  两个人在一起就容易多了
You know the Kelpie's easier with two.
或许你应该脱下你的衬衫
Perhaps you should take off your shirt?
别担心  我很快就会干透的
Don't worry, I'll dry off quickly enough.
看来有人需要发泄一下
Someone needed to let off some steam.
药膏  布蒂
Ointment, Bunty?
你再咬布蒂  就会有大麻烦了  先生
You bite Bunty again and there'll be trouble, mister.
-那是什么声   -我不知道
- What was that? - I don't know.
但我要你现在回家  布蒂
But I want you to go home now, Bunty.
-需要我想魔法部求助吗 -不  我要你回家  拜托
- Shall I call the Ministry? - No, I want you to go home. Please.
如果你能把它给我.
If you could just give it to me...
宝贝  如果你能把它给我.
Honey, if you could just give it to me.
-他不在乎  等等   -如果你能把它给我.
- He doesn't care. Hold it. - If you could just give it to me.
嘿
Hey...
纽特   快过来  你这个疯子
NEWT! Get over here, you maniac.
我们希望你不介意  纽特   我们就这样进来了
We hope you don't mind, Newt? We let ourselves in...
外面在下瓢泼大雨
it's raining out there-cats and dogs!
伦敦真冷
London's cold!
但你本应该遗忘这些的
But you were supposed to have been Obliviated!
我知道   但不管用  伙计
I know! It didn't work, pal.
我是说  你说过  魔药只会抹去不好的记忆
I mean, you said it, the potion only erases bad memories.
我没有什么不好的记忆
I didn't have any.
我是说  别误会  我是有一些奇怪的回忆
I mean, don't get me wrong, I had some weird ones...
但这个天使..
but this angel...
这位天使  她把所有不好的事情都告诉了我
this angel over here, she filled me in on all the bad parts.
我们就到这了  我想  是吧
And here we are, I guess, huh?
太棒了
This is wonderful!
是..蒂娜吗
Is ...Tina?
蒂娜
Tina?
哦  只有我们  亲爱的
Oh it's just us, honey.
只有我和雅各布
Me and Jacob.
要不我给你们做晚饭吧
Why don't I make us some dinner, huh?
好
Yes!
蒂娜和我没在说过话
Tina and I aren't talking.
为什么
Why?
哦  好吧  你知道  她发现了雅各布的事
Oh well, you know, she found out about Jacob and
我见过对方了 但她不喜欢这样
I seeing each other and she didn't like it,
因为法律
cause of the law
不允许这样做  也不允许和麻鸡约会
Not allowed oops, not allowed to date No-Majs,
不允许和他们结婚 的大废话
not allowed to marry them blah, blah, blah.
好吧  不管怎么说  她也是头晕目眩的  因为你
Well, she was all in a tizzy anyway, 'cause of you.
我
Me?
是啊  你  纽特
Yeah, you, Newt.
因为这本意乱情迷
It was in Spellbound.
我给你带来了
Here-I brought it for you-
纽特·斯卡曼德和未婚妻莉塔·莱斯特兰奇
Newt Scamander with fiancée, Leta Lestrange...
老兄  忒修斯和无名氏女子
brother, Theseus and unknown woman.
不  是忒修斯要娶的是莉塔  不是我
No. Theseus is marrying Leta, not me.
哦
Oh!
噢  噢亲爱的
Oh, oh dear.
哇
Wah.
所以蒂娜读了之后  然后她开始和别人约会了
So Tina read that, and she started dating someone else.
他是个傲罗  他的名字是阿基里斯·托列夫
He's an Auror. His name's Achilles Tolliver.
托列夫
Tolliver?
无论如何...我们很高兴来到这里  纽特
Anyway... We're real excited to be here, Newt.
这是  哦  这是我们的特别之旅
This is a, oh it's a special trip for us
你看  雅各布和我
You see, Jacob and I,
我们要结婚了
we're getting married.
我要和雅各布结婚了
I'm marrying Jacob!
你让他着迷了  不是吗
You've enchanted him, haven't you?
什么
What?
我没有
I have not.
你能别再读我的心了吗
Will you stop reading my mind?
奎妮  你违背他的意愿把他带到这里来的
Queenie, you've brought him here against his will.
哦  那是个无耻的指控
Oh, that is an outrageous accusation.
你看看他  他只是很开心
Look at him. He's just happy.
那你不会介意我...
Then you won't mind if I...
拜托  别这样
Please don't!
奎妮  如果他想和你结婚的话 你没什么好担心的
Queenie, you've got nothing to fear if he wants to get married.
我们可以解除魔法  他可以自己告诉我们
We can just lift the enchantment... and he can tell us himself.
你拿了什么
What you got there?
你要做什么   斯卡曼德先生  你打算怎么做
What gonna do? Whatchu gonna do with that, Mr. Scamander?
Surgito.
恭喜你  你订婚了  雅各布
Congratulations on your engagement, Jacob.
等等  什么
Wait, what?
哦不  你没有
Oh no, you didn't.
奎妮  稍等一下
Queen. A second.
奎妮
Queenie!
很高兴见到你
It's very nice to see you.
我现在到底在哪
Where the hell am I right now?
呃  呃  伦敦
Uh, uh, London.
哦   我一直想来这里
Oh! I always wanted to go here!
奎妮
Queenie!
哦  奎妮  亲爱的
Oh Queenie, honey.
好吧  我只是好奇  你什么时候叫醒我   在我们生了5个孩子之后
Well, I'm just curious, when were you going to wake me up? After we'd had five kids?
-想和你结婚有错吗   -好吧
- Why is it wrong to want to marry you? - Okay.
我只是想要一个家庭
To wanna have a family?
我只想要别人都有的东西  仅此而已
I just want what everyone else has, that's all.
好吧  等等.
Okay, wait..
我们谈过无数次了
We talked about this, like, a million times.
如果我们结婚了他们发现了  他们
If we get married and they find out, they're
会把你送进监狱的  亲爱的
gonna throw you in jail, sweetheart.
我不能这么做
I can't have that.
他们不喜欢我这样的人嫁给你这样的人
They don't like people like me marrying people like you.
我不是法师  我只是我自己
I ain't a wizard. I'm just me.
他们如果真的是进步派  他们会让我们好好结婚的
They're really progressive here, and they'll let us get married properly.
宝贝  你不需要让我着迷
Sweetheart, you don't need to enchant me.
我已经被你迷住了
I'm already enchanted!
我太爱你了
I love you so much.
-是吗   -是的
- Yeah?? - Yeah.
但我不能让你冒这么大的险  你知道吗
But I can't have you risking everything like this, you know?
你不比给我们选择的  亲爱的
You're not giving us a choice, sweetheart.
你没有给我选择的余地
You're not givin' me a choice.
我们中的一个必须勇敢  而你是个懦夫
One of us had to be brave, and you were being a coward!
我是个懦夫
I was being a coward?
如果我是个懦夫  你就是...
If I'm a coward, you're...
疯子
Crazy!
我没这么说...
I didn't say it...
你没必要这么做
You didn't have to.
不  我不是故意的  亲爱的
No, I didn't mean it, sweetheart.
你说了
Yeah, you did.
没有
No!
我要去看望我姐姐了
I'm gonna go see my sister.
好吧  去看你姐姐吧
Fine. See your sister.
-很好   -不   等等
- Fine. - No! Wait!
奎妮   不   奎妮
Queenie! No! Queenie!
我不是那个意思
I didn't mean it.
我什么都没说
I didn't say nothing.
巴黎
PARIS
我亲爱的奎妮  多么美丽的城市啊
My dear Queenie, what a beautiful city.
我在想你  蒂娜
I'm thinking of you, Tina.
嘿  纽特
Hey, Newt?
在这  雅各布  到这里来和我会和
Down here, Jacob. I'll be with you in a second.
我也有我自己的问题要处理
I got my own problems.
布蒂   别忘了给帕特里克喂药丸
BUNTY! DON'T FORGET TO GIVE PATRICK PELLETS.
奎妮留了张明信片
Queenie left a postcard.
蒂娜在巴黎找克雷登斯
Tina's in Paris looking for Credence.
太好了
Genius!
奎妮要直接去找蒂娜
Queenie's gonna go straight for Tina.
好吧  我们要去法国了  伙计
Okay, we're going to France, pal!
等等  我去拿我的夹克
Hold on. I'll get my jacket.
帮你拿到了
I've got it.
哦  真好
Oh. Beautiful.
布蒂  我去巴黎了  带走了一个嗅嗅  纽特
BUNTY, GONE TO PARIS. HAVE TAKEN NIFFLERS WITH ME. NEWT.
纳吉尼
Nagini.
克雷登斯
Credence.
我想我知道她在哪儿
I think I know where she is.
我们今晚就逃之夭夭
We escape tonight.
嘿
Hey.
我告诉过你离她远点  小子
I've told you to stay away from her, boy.
我说过你可以休息了吗
Did I say you could take a break?
把卡帕清理干净
Clean out the Kappa.
你  准备好
And you, get ready!
下一个是我们的怪胎和怪人秀
Next in our little show of freaks and oddities...
我向你们介绍.
I present to you...
马德里图斯
a Maledictus!
曾经被困在印度尼西亚的丛林里
Once trapped in the jungles of Indonesia,
她是一个血液诅咒的携带者
she is the carrier of a blood curse.
这样的存在是注定 一生都要背负着这种诅咒的
Such Under-beings are destined, through the course of their lives...
注定会永远变成一个怪兽
to turn permanently into beasts.
现在他看起来很漂亮 对吗
But look at her. So beautiful, yes?
太令人向往了
So desirable.
但很快她就会永远被困在一个完全不同的身体里
But soon she will be trapped forever in a very different body.
每天晚上  当她睡着的时候.
Every night, when she sleeps...
女士们还有先生们
mesdames et messieurs...
她就会被迫成为
She is forced to become...
随着时间的推移  她将无法转变回来
Over time, she will not be able to transform back.
她将永远被困在蛇的身体里
She will be forever trapped in the body of a snake.
克雷登斯
Credence!
打包走人
Pack it up!
巴黎已经不能待了
Paris is done for us now.
那个小子  你对他了解多少
The boy with the Maledictus, what do you know about him?
他在找他妈妈
He's looking for his mother.
我这所有的怪物都认为他们能回家
All my freaks think they can go home.
好吧  我们走
Okay, let's go.
听着  我想我们都去马戏团是出于同样的原因  先生 你叫什么
Look, I think we were both at the circus for the same reason, monsieur ...?
卡玛  尤瑟夫·卡玛
Kama. Yusuf Kama.
你说的没错
And you think right.
-你找克雷登斯做什么   -和你一样
- What do you want with Credence? - The same as you.
-哪个   -为了证明这个男孩是谁
- Which is? - To prove who the boy really is.
如果关于他身份的谣言是正确的
If the rumors of his identity are correct, he and
他和我是远亲
I are distantly related.
我是我家族里纯种血统的最后一个男性
I am the last male of my pure-blooded line.
所以  如果谣言是对的  那么他也是
And so, if the rumors are correct, is he.
你读过第谷·多多斯的预言吗
Have you read The Predictions of Tycho Dodonus?
是啊  但那是诗  不是证据
Yeah. But that's poetry, not proof.
如果我能给你看些更好的
If I could show you something better
更具体的  能证明他是谁的东西
more concrete, something that proves who he is
欧洲和美国的部会让他活着吗
would the Ministries of Europe and America let him live?
可能吧
They might.
那就来吧
Then come.
所以…
So...
克里登斯 巴波
Credence Barebone.
他的一生几乎被抚养她的女人给毁了
Nearly destroyed by the woman who raised him.
然而现在他却在寻找生他的母亲
Yet now he seeks the mother who bore him.
他渴望有个家
He's desperate for family.
他渴望被关爱
He's desperate for love.
他是我们胜利的关键
He's the key to our victory.
好吧  我们知道这小子在哪  不是吗
Well, we know where the boy is, don't we?
-我们为什么不抓住他然后离开   -他必须要自愿的来找我
- Why don't we grab him and leave! - He must come to me freely...
他会的
and he will.
这条路已经铺好了  他正在沿着这条路走
The path has been laid, and he is following it.
会让他找到我的线索
The trail that will lead him to me,
以及他是谁 还有他那神秘的身份
and the strange and glorious truth of who he is.
为什么他这么重要
Why is he so important?
对我们的事业构成最大的威胁是谁
Who represents the greatest threat to our cause?
阿不思·邓布利多
Albus Dumbledore.
如果我让你现在去学校...去他那里
If I asked you now to go to the school... where he is
为我藏起来杀了他  你会为我这么做吗  卡尔
hiding and kill him for me, would you do it for me, Krall?
克雷登斯是唯一活着的实体
Credence is the only entity alive...
谁能杀了他
who can kill him.
你真的认为他能杀死伟大的..
You really think that he can kill the great...
会杀了阿不思·邓布利多吗
can kill Albus Dumbledore?
我知道他可以
I know he can.
但是当那发生的时候你会和我们在一起吗  卡尔
But will you be with us when that happens, Krall?
你还会吗
Will you?
雅各布  蒂娜见过的那个人.
Jacob, that man Tina's been seeing...
别担心  她会见到你的
Don't worry, she's gonna see you.
她会看到我们四个在一起
And she'll see the four of us together, it'll be just
又像在纽约一样  不用担心
like New York all over again. Don't worry about it.
-奎妮说 他是个傲罗  -好吧  他是个傲罗  那又怎样
- Yes, but he's an Auror, Queenie said? - Yeah, he's an Auror. So what?
别担心他
Don't worry about him.
如果我见到她  你觉得我该对她说什么
What do you think I should say to her, if I see her?
哦  好吧  最好还是不要提前想好
Oh, well, it's best not to plan these things.
到时候想说什么就说什么吧
You know, you just say whatever comes to you in the moment.
她的眼睛就像火蜥蜴一样
She has eyes just like a salamander.
别这么说
Don't say that.
不行  听着  你只要告诉她你想她
Nah, look, you just tell her that you missed her.
是啊  然后你大老远跑到巴黎就是为了找到她
Right, and then you came all the way to Paris just to find her.
她会喜欢的
She'll love that.
然后  告诉她你晚上会因为想起她而失眠
And then, tell her you're losing sleep at night for thinking of her.
别再说什么火蜥蜴的事  好吗
Just don't say anything about no salamanders, all right?
对 我可以做到
Right. Okay.
嘿  嘿  嘿  一切都会好起来的
Hey, hey, hey. It's gonna be all right.
我们是一伙的  伙计
We're in this together, pal.
好吧  我会帮你的  我要帮你找到蒂娜  然后去找到奎妮
Okay, I'm gonna help you out. I'm gonna help you find Tina, find Queenie,
我们都会高兴的  就像以前一样
and we'll all be happy again. Just like old times.
他是谁
Who is this guy?
他是我在没有文件的情况下离开这个国家的唯一途径
He's the only way I can leave the country without documentation.
你应该没有晕动症吧  是吗
Now, you don't suffer from motion sickness, do you?
我晕船  纽特
I don't do well on boats, Newt.
不会有事的
You'll be fine.
赶紧的  一分钟后就要出发
Stir your stumps-it leaves in one minute!
五十加隆
Fifty Galleons.
不  我们说好的三十
No, we said thirty.
三十是去法国的路费
Thirty to go to France,
剩下的二十是封口费 我不告诉任何人我看见纽特·斯卡曼德非法离开了这个国家
twenty not to tell anyone, I seen Newt Scamander leaving the country illegally.
出名的代价  伙计
Price of fame, pal.
还有十秒钟
Ten seconds.
雅各伯
Jacob.
七
Seven.
六
Six
四
Four.
三
Three.
二  一
Two. One.
我不喜欢波特基 纽特
I didn't like that Portkey, Newt.
所以你一直在抱怨
So you keep saying.
跟我来
Follow me.
Confundus.
快点  再过几分钟就没效果了
Come on. That'll wear off in a few minutes.
Appare vestigium.
释放嗅嗅
Accio Niffler...
快去找找   快去找找
Get looking. Oi! Get looking.
这是个卡帕
That's a Kappa.
这是个日本水妖
That's a Japanese water demon.
蒂娜
Tina?
Tina?!
你发现了什么
What have you found?
我们现在 在舔脏东西吗
And we're licking the dirt now. Revelio.
纽特...这是什么东西
Newt... what made those?
那是邹武
That is a Zouwu.
是一种中国生物  它们的速度和威力都令人难以置信
It's a Chinese creature. They are incredibly fast and incredibly powerful.
他们能一天能走一千里路
They can travel a thousand miles in a day
只要一步就可以让你从巴黎的一个地方跳到下一个地方
and this one could take you from one part of Paris to the next in a single leap.
哦  好孩子
Oh, good boy.
雅各布  她在这里  蒂娜曾站在这里
Jacob, she was here. Tina stood here.
她的脚很窄  你注意到了吗
She has incredibly narrow feet, have you noticed?
我可看不出来
Can't say that I have.
后来有人朝她走过来
Then someone came towards her.
Avenseguim.
-跟着那羽毛走   -什么
- Follow that feather. - What?
-雅各布  跟着羽毛走   -跟着羽毛走
- Jacob, follow the feather. - Follow the feather.
它去哪儿   啊  收回嗅嗅
Where is he? Ah, Accio Niffler.
把水桶扔了
Let go of the bucket!
欢迎来到魔法事务部
Bienvenue Au Ministère des Affaires Magiques.
对不起  我完全不知道你刚才说了什么
I'm sorry, I don't know what you just said at all.
欢迎来到法国魔法部  你来这里是做什么的
Welcome to the French Ministry of Magic. What is your business, please?
我要找蒂娜·戈德斯坦
I need to speak to Tina Goldstein.
她正在办案是一个美国傲罗
She's an American Auror working on a case here.
我们这里没有蒂娜·戈德斯坦
We have no Tina Goldstein here.
不  这.. 我很抱歉这一定是搞错了
No, it's... I'm sorry there must be some sort of mistake.
我知道她在巴黎  她给我寄了张明信片
See, I know she's in Paris, she sent me a postcard.
我带来了  我可以拿给你看  或许你
I brought it, I can show it to you. Maybe you
你能帮我在这里找到她吗   就在这里
can help me find her here? It's just in here.
哦  倒霉
Oh rabbits!
请稍等一下
If you can just wait one moment!
我知道它就在这里的某个地方  我肯定带了  在哪里
I know it's in here somewhere. I definitely packed it. Where?
稍等一下
One second.
你先请
Please.
我们能不能停下来喝杯咖啡  或者
Could we at least stop for a coffee, or like a...
现在不行  雅各布
Not now, Jacob.
往这边走  快点
This way. Come on.
吃巧克力面包   半根羊角面包  或者是一个棒棒糖
Pain Au chocolat? Half a croissant, or like, a bonbon?
往这边走
This way.
雅各伯
Jacob!
Jacob?
夫人
Madame?
夫人  你还好吗
Tout Va bien, Madame?
她回来了
She's home.
谁在那里
Qui est l?
夫人  请听我说 你的儿子来了
C'est votre fils, madame.
你是谁
Qui êtes-vous?
你是艾玛吗
Are you Irma?
你...   你是艾玛·杜加德吗
Are you ...? Are you Irma Dugard?
打扰了  我的领养纸上是你的名字
I'm sorry. Your name is on my adoption paper.
你都知道什么
Does this make sense?
你把我交给了纽约的巴瑞斯太太
You gave me to Mrs. Barebone in New York.
我不是你妈妈
I am not your mother.
我只是个仆人
I was only a servant.
你真是个帅气的孩子
You were so beautiful baby.
你真是个帅气的小伙
And you are a beautiful man.
我很想你
I have missed you.
为什么他们不想要我
Why didn't they want me?
但为什么你的名字会出现在我的收养纸上
But why is your name on my adoption paper?
我本应该带你去找巴瑞斯太太的
I took you to Mrs. Barebone
因为她会照顾你的
because she was supposed to look after you.
她死了
She's dead.
那小子怎么样
How did the boy take it?
他很敏感
He's sensitive.
魔法部知道我出了差错  不会高兴的
The Ministry won't be happy when I tell them I've missed.
-他们知道我的名声...  -听我说..
- They know my reputation.. - Listen to me...
那些懦夫的不赞成是对勇敢的人的赞扬
The disapproval of cowards is praise to the brave.
当法师统治世界的时候  你的名字将会以荣耀的形式写出来
Your name will be written in glory when wizards rule the world.
而这个时间越来越近了
And the clock is ticking faster.
你照看着克雷登斯
You watch over Credence.
保护他的安全
Keep him safe.
为了更伟大的利益
For the greater good.
你知道  我想念奎妮什么吗
You know what I miss about Queenie?
什么都想
Everything.
我甚至怀念那些让我发疯的东西
I even miss the stuff that drove me nuts.
就像读心术一样
Like the mind reading.
我很幸运有她这样的人
I was lucky to have someone like her
对我想的任何事都感兴趣
even interested in anything I thought.
你知道我的意思吗
You know what I mean?
什么
Sorry?
我是说  你确定我们要找的人在这里
I was saying, you're sure the guy is here that we're looking for?
当然  羽毛是这么表现得
Definitely. The feather says so.
-我们要找的人是他吗   -是的
- Is that the guy we're looking for? - Yes.
先生
Sire.
呃..你好  你好  先生
Err... bonjour. Bonjour, monsieur.
等等  不  等等
Oh wait, no, sorry!
我们只是想知道你会不会遇到  呃  我们的一个朋友..
We were just wondering if you'd come across uh, a friend of ours...
蒂娜·戈德斯坦
Tina Goldstein.
先生  巴黎可是个大城市
Monsieur, Paris is a large city.
她是个傲罗
She's an Auror..
当傲罗失踪时  魔法部会来找她的  所以…
When Aurors go missing, the Ministry tend to come looking. So...
好吧  现在我想我们最好还是报告她失踪了吧
No, now I suppose it would probably be better if we just report her absence.
高个子
Is she tall?
黑发
Dark rather...
-有点紧张   -漂亮
- intense? - Beautiful.
是的  我想说的是
Yeah, what I meant to say-
她非常 非常漂亮
she's very-very pretty!
我想我昨晚见过这样的人
I think I saw someone like this last night.
-也许我能带你去找她   -如果你不介意的话  那就.
- Perhaps if I showed you where? - If you wouldn't mind. That would be...
-那就太好了   -当然
- That would be lovely. - Sure.
蒂娜
Tina?
纽特
Newt!
我很抱歉  斯卡曼德先生
My apologies, Mr. Scamander!
一旦克雷登斯死了  我就会回来释放你
I shall return and release you once Credence is dead!
卡玛  等等
Kama, wait!
你看  不是他死就是我亡
You see, either he dies... or I do.
不  不  不
No, no, no.
哦不  不  不  不
Oh no. No, no, no.
好吧  营救行动看来出了点偏差
Well, that's not the best start to a rescue attempt.
这是一次营救行动吗
This was a rescue attempt?
你刚刚让我失去了我唯一的线索
You've just lost me my only lead.
好吧  在我们出现之前审讯进行得怎么样了
Well, how was the interrogation going before we turned up?
纽特
Newt!
干得好  皮克
Well done, Pick.
-所以说你需要这个人   -是的
- So, you need this man, you say? - Yeah.
我想这个人知道克雷登斯在哪里  斯卡曼德先生
I think this man knows where Credence is, Mr. Scamander.
好吧  那就是邹武了
Well, that'll be the Zouwu.
快点  纽特  离开那里
Come on, Newt, get out of there!
你上次犯的三个最大的错误是什么
What were the three biggest mistakes that you made last time?
出其不意  先生
Caught by surprise, sir.
还有什么
What else?
在反击之前没有退缩  先生
Didn't parry before counter-curse, sir.
很好  最后一个呢
Very good. And the last one...
也是最重要的一个
the most important one?
没有从前两个中学到东西
Not learning from the first two.
这是学校  你没有权利
This is a school, you've no right
我是魔法执法部门的负责人  我有权利去任何我想去的地方
I'm the Head of Magical Law Enforcement and I have the right to go wherever I please.
都出去
Out of here.
请和麦格教授一起出去
Go with Professor McGonagall, please.
他是我们最好的老师
He's the best teacher we've got.
-谢谢  麦克拉根   -出去
- Thanks, McClaggan. - Get out!
快来  麦克拉根
Come, McClaggan.
纽特·斯卡曼德在巴黎
Newt Scamander is in Paris.
真的
Really?
别装了  我知道他是听你的命令来的
Cut the pretense. I know he's there on your orders.
如果你有幸教过他的话
If you'd ever had the pleasure to teach him, you'd
你就知道纽特不是一个听话的人
know Newt is not a great follower of orders.
你读过第谷·多多斯的预言吗
You've read The Predictions of Tycho Dodonus??
很多年前读过
Many years ago.
"儿子被残忍放逐 女儿带着绝望归来"
"A son cruelly banished Despair of the daughter"
-归来   -是的  我知道了
- Return. - Yes, I know it.
有传言说这个预言指的是默默然
There's a rumor this prediction refers to the Obscurial.
他们说格林德沃想要.
They say that Grindelwald wants.
一个高贵的追随者  我听说过这个谣言
A highborn henchman. I've heard the rumor.
然而  斯卡曼德出现在的地方默默然都待过  是为了保护他
And yet Scamander appears wherever the Obscurial goes, to protect him.
与此同时  你已经建立了一个相当小型的国际联络网
Meanwhile you have built up quite a little network of international contacts.
不管你监视我和我朋友多久了
However long you keep me and my friends under surveillance...
你不会发现有针对你的阴谋的  崔佛斯
You're not going to discover plots against you, Travers.
因为我们的目的一样 打败格林德沃
Because we want the same thing: the defeat of Grindelwald.
但我警告你  你的镇压和暴力政策
But I warn you, your policies of suppression and violence
会把支持者推到他怀里
are pushing supporters into his arms.
我对你的警告不感兴趣
I'm not interested in your warnings!
现在  我本不想说的  因为
Now, it pains me to say it, because
好吧  我不喜欢你
Well, I don't like you.
但是…
But...
你是唯一和他一样的法师
you are the only wizard who is his equal.
我需要你去对抗他
I need you to fight him.
我不行
I cannot.
就因为这个吗
Because of this?
你和格林德沃就像兄弟一样亲密
You and Grindelwald were as close as brothers.
我们比兄弟更亲密
We were closer than brothers.
你会和他对抗吗
Will you fight him?
我不能
I can't.
那你就选择了你的一边
Then you have chosen your side.
从现在开始  我将知道你施的每一个咒语
From now on, I shall know every spell you cast..
我要加倍监视你
I'm doubling the watch on you
你将不再教授黑魔法防御术
and you will no longer teach Defense Against the Dark Arts.
莉塔在哪   我们要去巴黎
Where's Leta? We need to go to Paris!
忒修斯
Theseus.
忒修斯  如果格林德沃召集集会..
Theseus, if Grindelwald calls a rally...
不要阻止他
don't try and break it up.
别让崔佛斯派你去
Don't let Travers send you in there.
如果你曾经信任过我的话
If you ever trusted me...
忒修斯   忒修斯
Theseus! Theseus!
即使是利斯特兰奇也让我觉得恶心
Even Lestranges makes me feel sick.
你知道她每个假期都呆在这里
You know she stays here every vacation.
她的家人其实并不想要她回家
Her family don't actually want her home.
我不怪他们  她太烦人了
I don't blame them, she's so annoying.
你上周见过她吗
- Did you see her last week? - Oscausi!
麦格教授   莱斯特兰奇又干坏事了
Professor McGonagall! Lestrange has done it again!
莱斯特兰奇 别跑了
Lestrange, stop running!
-莱斯特兰奇 不听话的孩子   站住   -快给我回来
- Lestrange! Disobedient children! Stop! - She needs to come back!
斯莱特林学院的耻辱
Shame on the House of Slytherin.
一百分   两百
A hundred points! Two hundred!
快回来  马上
Get back here, right now!
站住 站住 回来
Stop! Stop it! Stop it! You stop it! Get back!
教授  莱斯特兰奇  她太过分了
Miss, it was Lestrange. She's horrible!
斯卡曼德...你为什么不收拾行李
Scamander... why aren't you packing?
我不回家了
I'm not going home.
为什么不呢
Why not?
它需要我
He needs me.
它伤得很重
It was hurt.
这是什么
What is that?
一只渡鸦
A raven chick.
渡鸦不是你家族的象征吗
Isn't Raven your family emblem.
是的
Yes it is.
好吧  纽特
All right, Newt.
勇敢点
Be brave.
太不寻常了
That's an unusual one.
那么  斯卡曼德先生最怕的是什么呢
So Mrs. Scamander fears what more than anything else in the world?
必须在办公室工作  教授
Having to work in an office, sir.
好吧  纽特
Go ahead, Newt.
Riddikulus
干得好
Well done.
干得好   莉塔
Good job. Leta?
这只是一个幻形怪
It's only a Boggart,
不会伤害你的
it can't hurt you.
所有人都害怕某些东西
Everyone's scared of something
我一直期待看她出丑
I've been looking forward to this.
我不想谈这个
I don't want to talk about it!
他们认识我  不然就躲起来
They know me, or they'd hide.
它们只在有法杖的树上筑巢
They only nest in trees with wand quality wood,
你知道吗
did you know that?
他们的社会生活非常复杂
And they have very complex social lives.
如果你观察他们足够长的时间  你就会意识到
If you watch them for long enough, you realize.
你好  莉塔
Hello, Leta.
这是个惊喜吗
This is a surprise.
没想到我会在教室里吗
Finding me in a classroom?
我是个这么差的学生吗
Was I such a bad student?
相反  你是我最聪明的学生之一
On the contrary, you were one of my cleverest
我说的差  不是愚蠢
I said bad, not stupid.
不用回答了
Don't bother answering.
-我知道你从来都不喜欢我  -你错了
- I know you never liked me.. - Well, you're wrong.
我从没想过你是坏的
I never thought you bad.
那么你就是个例外  其他人都这么觉得
You were alone, then. Everybody else did.
他们是对的
And they were right.
我是邪恶的
I was wicked.
莉塔  我知道关于你弟弟考维斯的谣言你一定很痛苦
Leta, I know how painful the rumors about your brother Corvus must
为了你
be for you.
不  你不明白  除非你有个兄弟也死了
No, you don't. Not unless you had a brother who died too.
对我来说  死的是我妹妹
In my case, it was my sister.
你爱她吗
Did you love her?
我对她的关心不够多
Not as well as I should have done.
释怀什么时候也不晚
Never too late to free yourself.
我听说忏悔是一种解脱  能如释重负
Confession is a relief, I'm told. A great weight lifted.
后悔是我永远的伴侣
Regret is my constant companion.
别让它占据了你
Do not let it become yours.
不用了  谢谢
Oh No, thank you.
你人真好  但是.
Well, you've been real kind, but...
我姐姐蒂娜可能很担心我
my sister Tina's probably worried sick about me...
你知道的  她会疯狂敲门找我的
you know, banging on all the doors and things...
所以我想  我最好还是告辞吧
so I think I'd better be going.
但你还没见过这里的男主人呢
But you haven't met your host.
哦  你结婚了吗
Oh, are you married?
不如是说...五体投地
Let's say... deeply committed.
你看  我不知道你是不是在开玩笑
You see, I can't tell if you're making a joke
或是你们法国人就这样
or if you're just... French.
嘿  别闹了
Hey, knock it off.
你就呆在那里
You stay right there.
我知道你是什么人
I know what you are.
奎妮
Quennie.
我们不是来伤害你的
We are not here to hurt you.
我们只想帮你
We only want to help you.
你离家太远了  太远了
You're so very, very far from home.
远离你所爱的一切  离开那个舒服地方
Far away from everything you love. Everything that was comfortable.
我永远不会让你受到伤害  永远不会
I would never see you harmed, ever.
你姐姐是傲罗  不是你的错
It is not your fault that your sister is an Auror.
我真希望你现在能和我们在一起
I wish you were working with me now towards a
创建一个公开的法师世界
world where we wizards are free to live openly,
去自由地爱
and to love freely.
你是无辜的
You are an innocent.
所以现在走吧
So go now.
离开这里
Leave this place.
嘿  纽特  伙计
Hey, Newt, buddy.
蒂娜在上面  她看起来满寂寞的
Tina's up here. She's all by her lonesome
或许你能过来陪着她
and maybe you want to come up and keep her company?
我在找吃的  但什么也没找到  所以  我想我
I've been looking for food, and I ain't found any. So, I guess I'm
上楼去试试我的运气 也许阁楼会有东西
gonna go upstairs and try my luck in the-I dunno-the attic!
你会没事的
You're all right. Relaxio.
好吧
Okay.
用了白藓 它的反应还不错
She's responded well to the Dittany.
你看  它天生就是跑步的料
She was born to run, you see.
我觉得它只是缺乏自信
I think she's just lacking in confidence
斯卡曼德先生  你的箱子里有什么能让他起死回生的东西吗
Mr. Scamander, have you got anything in your case that might help revive this man?
我需要问他一些问题
I need to question him.
我想他知道克雷登斯的真实身份
I think he knows who Credence really is.
他手上的伤疤表明他的誓言牢不可破
The scars on his hand suggest an unbreakable vow...
-牢不可破的誓言   -牢不可破的誓言  我也注意到了
- an unbreakable vow. - Unbreakable vow. I noticed that too.
Lumos
那是什么
What was that?
在下水道里一定有一条水龙
There must be a water dragon in that sewer
它们携带着这些寄生虫  你看  他们…
they carry these parasites, you see. They...
-雅各布   -干嘛
- Jacob? - Yeah?
在我箱子的那个口袋里  你会找到一把镊子
In my case, in the pocket there, you'll find a pair of tweezers.
镊子
Tweezers?
-它们又薄又尖  -又薄又尖的东西
- They're thin and pointy... - Thin, little pointy things.
是的  我知道镊子是什么
Yes, I know what tweezers are.
你可能不想看这个场景
You might not want to watch this...
没事的
I can handle it.
来吧
Come on.
哦  别这样
Oh come on.
雅各布  你能帮我拿一下吗
Jacob, will you take that for me?
挺像章鱼的
Calamari..
我必须杀了他
I must kill him.
谁
Who?
克雷登斯
Credence?
他可能需要几个小时才能康复  寄生虫的毒性很强
It may take him a few hours to recover. The parasite's poison is quite strong.
我要带着我所有发现的东西回魔法部去
I'll have to go back to the Ministry with what I've got.
很高兴再次见到你  斯卡曼德先生
It was nice to see you again, Mr. Scamander.
嘿  等一下  好吗  等等
Hey, hold on one second, will you? Well, hold on!
等等   蒂娜
Wait! Tina!
你没说什么火蜥蜴吧
You didn't mention salamanders, did you?
没说  她就是这么走了  我不知道..
No, she just ran. I don't know...
所以你就去追她啊
So you chase after her!
蒂娜  拜托  听我说
Tina. Please, just listen to me-
斯卡曼德先生  我要去和魔法部的人谈谈
Mr. Scamander, I need to go talk to the Ministry.
我知道你对傲罗的态度
And I know how you feel about Aurors.
我在信中表达自己的方式可能有点强硬
I may have been a little strong in the way that I expressed myself in that letters.
那个的短语是怎么说来着   一群装腔作势的伪君子
What was the exact phrase? “A bunch of careerist hypocrites?
我很抱歉  但我不喜欢别人
I'm sorry, but I can't admire people
他们害怕或误解的一切问题的答案就是扼杀它
whose answer to everything that they fear or misunderstand is kill it?
我是个傲罗  我不是那样的人
I'm an Auror and I don't...
那是因为你是中间的那个头
Yes, and that's because you've gone middle head!
你说什么
Excuse me?
这是一个来自一个三个头的如尼纹蛇说法
It's an expression derived from the three heads of the Runespoor.
中间那个代表幻想者
The middle one is a visionary.
除了你  欧洲的每一个傲罗都希望克雷登斯死掉  你现在就是中间那个头
Every Auror in Europe wants Credence dead-except you. You've gone middle head.
现在谁会用这个词呢  斯卡曼德先生
Who else uses that expression, Mr. Scamander?
我想可能只有我吧
I think it might just be me.
是格林德沃  他在召唤追随者
It's Grindelwald. He's calling his followers.
太迟了
It's too late.
格林德沃来找克雷登斯了
Grindelwald's come for Credence.
他可能已经抓到他了
He might already have him.
现在还不算太晚  我们还是可以先找到他的
It's not too late. We can still get to him first.
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
法国魔法部
The French Ministry of Magic.
那是克雷登斯最不愿意去的地方
That's the last place Credence would go!
在蒂娜部门藏着一个盒子
There's a box hidden at the Ministry Tina.
这是一个可以告诉我们克雷登斯是谁的盒子
It's a box that can tell us who Credence really is.
盒子   你在说什么
A box? What are you talking about?
相信我
Trust me.
你想出来吗   就一会儿
You wanna come out? Just for a little while?
克雷斯登
Credence.
-嘘   -你想要什么
- Shh. - What do you want?
从你那里吗
From you?
什么都不要
Nothing.
但我有东西给你
For you?
我从未拥有的一切
Everything I never had.
但你想要什么  我的孩子
But what is it you want, my boy?
我想知道我是谁
I want to know who I am.
在这里你会找到你真实身份的证据
This is where you will find proof of your true identity.
今晚来拉雪兹公墓  你会发现真相的
Come to Père Lachaise tonight and you will discover the truth.
父亲  你为什么要这么对我
Father... why did you make me ...?
等等
Wait!
恐怕我们家里没有食物了
I'm afraid we keep no food in the house.
你是鬼吗
Are you a ghost?
不  不  我是活人
No, no, I am alive,
但我是炼金术士  所以我是不朽的
but I am an alchemist, and therefore immortal.
你看起来一点也不像三十七十五岁以上的人
You don't look a day over three-seventy-five.
嘿  抱歉我们没敲门
Hey, sorry we didn't knock.
不  没关系
No, no matter.
阿不思告诉我有些朋友可能会来
Albus told me some friends might be dropping in.
尼古拉斯·弗拉梅尔
Nicolas Flamel.
-雅各布·科瓦尔斯基   -哦
- Jacob Kowalski. - Oh.
-对不起   -没事的
- I'm Sorry. - It's alright.
我不是有意的
I didn't.
啊
Ah!
至少  我们能看到了一些进展
At last, we see some developments!
我以前见过这个
I've seen one of these before.
是在集市上
It was at the fair.
那里有一位夫人  她戴着面纱  我给了她五分钱
There was this dame there, and she had a veil.. I gave her a nickel and
她告诉我  我的未来
she told me about my future.
实际上她算的实在是差太多了
And she missed out on quite a bit actually.
等等   我认识他  是那个孩子  那是克雷登斯
Wait a minute! I know him. That's that kid. That's Credence
天啊
Jesus.
嘿   是奎妮   她来了
Hey! That's Queenie! There she is
嗨  宝贝
Hi, baby!
这是在哪   就在这吗
Where is this? Is this-is this here?
对  这是莱斯特兰奇家的墓
Yes. This is the Lestrange tomb.
它位于拉雪兹公墓
It lies in the cemetery of Père Lachaise
我来了  宝贝  呆在那儿别动
I'm coming, baby. Stay right there.
谢谢  谢谢  弗拉梅尔先生
Thank you, thank you, Mr. Flamel!
-啊   -哦  我很抱歉   我很抱歉
- Ahh! - Ooh no. I'm sorry! I'm sorry, okay?
哦 替我照看一下章鱼先生
Oh-look after Mr. Tentacles for me.
-哦  抱歉  我得走了   -求你了  你不能去墓地
- Oh no. I'm sorry, I gotta go. - Please, you must not go to the cemetery!
哦  亲爱的
Oh dear
-发生什么事了   -他说的一切都发生了
- What's happening? - Exactly what he said would happen.
格林德沃今晚在墓地集会  将会有很多人死的
Grindelwald rallies at the cemetery tonight, and there will be death!
-那你必须得去   -什么
- Then you gotta go! - What?
我有两百年没用过了
I haven't seen action in two hundred years...
弗拉梅尔  你能做到的  我们相信你
Flamel, you can do this. We believe in you.
盒子在祖先档案室  蒂娜
The box is in the ancestral records room, Tina.
所以  就在地下三层
So, three floors down.
变脸药剂吗
Is that Polyjuice?
这个刚好能让我进去
Just enough to get me inside.
-这是谁...   -那是我哥哥  忒修斯
- Who...? - That's my brother, Theseus.
他是个傲罗
He's an Auror.
喜欢拥抱
And a hugger.
出什么事了
What's happening?
格林德沃在集结  我们不知道在哪  但我们认为是今晚
Grindelwald's rallying. We don't know where, but we think it's tonight.
-小心点   -当然
- Be careful. - Of course.
-答应我你会小心的   -当然  我会小心的
- Promise me you'll be careful. - Of course, I'm going to be careful.
听着  我想让你听我说
Listen, I want you to hear this from me.
他们认为那个克雷登斯的男孩可能是你失踪的弟弟
They think that Credence boy might be your missing brother.
-我弟弟死了  他死了  -我知道  我知道
- My brother is dead. He died.. - I know. I know.
要我说多少次  忒修斯
How many times, Theseus?
这些记录  这些记录会证明的
And the records, the records will prove that,
好吧
okay?
-他们不会撒谎   -忒修斯
- They can't lie. - Theseus.
我要逮捕集会上的每一个人
I want every person at that rally arrested...
-如果他们抵抗...  -先生 冒昧的问一句 但是如果我们的人去太多
- If they resist... - Sir-forgive me but if we go in too heavy,
-难道不会增加风险吗   -就这么做吧
- don't we run the risk of adding to the. - Just do it.
我想你不可能在法国魔法部的房子里暂时消失吧  你可以吗
I don't suppose you can Disapparate on Ministry premises in France, can you?
不行
No.
可惜
Pity.
-纽特   -是的  我知道  我知道有
- Newt. - Yes, I know. I know there's-
紧急情况   紧急情况   逃亡法师
Emergency! Emergency! A tracked wizard,
纽特  斯卡曼德  进入魔法部了
Newt Scamander, has entered the Department of Magic!
纽特
Newt!
他是你哥哥
That's your brother?
是的  我想我在信中提到过
Yes, I think I may have mentioned in my letters
我们的关系很复杂
that we have quite a complicated relationship.
纽特  站住
Newt, stop!
-他想杀了你吗   -经常
- Does he want to kill you? - Frequently.
他需要控制自己的脾气
He needs to control his temper!
我想那可能是我一生中最美好的时刻
I think that might have been the best moment of my life.
奎妮
Quennie?
奎妮  亲爱的
Queenie, honey?
别动
Don't.
Don't move.
需要帮助吗
Puis-je vous aider?
是的  他是莉塔 莱斯特兰奇
Yes, this is Leta Lestrange.
我是她的..
And-I'm her...
未婚夫
Fianc?
请进
In you go.
谢谢
Thank you.
蒂娜  关于订婚的事.
Tina, about that fiancée business...
抱歉  是的  我应该祝贺你的
Sorry, yeah. I should have congratulated you.
不  那是...
- No, that's... - Lumos.
莱斯特兰奇
Lestrange.
蒂娜  关于莉塔.
Tina, about Leta...
是的  我刚说过  我为你感到高兴
Yes, I've just said, I am happy for you.
好了  好了  别装做你很高心的样子了
Yeah, well, I don't. Please don't be happy.
呃  不  不  我很抱歉  我不..
Uh, no, no. I'm sorry. I don't...
呃  很明显  我很明显我希望你是
Uh, obviously, I obviously I want you to be.
我听说了你的情况
And I hear that you are now.
呃  那太好了
Uh, which is wonderful.
抱歉  我想说的是
Sorry. What I'm trying to say is,
我不想让你为我的快乐而高兴  因为我而
I don't want you to be happy that I am happy because I'm not
快乐
happy.
我没订婚
Or engaged.
-什么   -那本愚蠢的杂志弄错了
- What? - It was a mistake in a stupid magazine.
我哥哥6月6日要和莉塔结婚  我是去
My brother's marrying Leta, June the sixth... I'm supposed
去做一个伴郎的  这事挺滑稽的
to be best man Which is sort of mildly hilarious.
他觉得你是来赢回她的吗
Does he think you're here to win her back?
-你是来赢回她的吗   -不  我是来
- Are you here to win her back? - No, I'm here to...
你知道吗  你的眼睛真的
you know, your eyes really are.
真的什么
Are what?
还是不说了
I'm not supposed to say.
纽特  我读了你的书  还有你...
Newt, I read your book, and did you...
我还有你的照片 等等  你读了吗
I still have a picture of you-wait, did you read?
还有这个
I got this...
我是说  这只是你在报纸上的照片
I mean, it's just a picture of you from the paper.
这很有趣  因为你的眼睛通过新闻纸的印刷
It's interesting because your eyes in newsprint...
你看  在现实中他们有这样的效果  蒂娜
See, in reality they have this effect in them, Tina,
就像水里的火  在黑暗中的水
it's like fire in water, in dark water..
我只看到过一次
I've only ever seen that.
我是在那个...
I've only ever seen that in...
火蜥蜴吗
Salamanders?
走
Come.
莱斯特兰奇
Lestrange.
记录被移到拉雪兹公墓的莱斯特兰奇家族墓地
Records moved to Lestrange family tomb at Père Lachaise.
Circumrota.
你好  纽特
Hello, Newt.
你好  莉塔
Hello, Leta
嗨
Hi.
哦不
Oh no.
那是什么猫
What kind of cats are those?
它们不是猫
These aren't cats.
他们是玛戈达  带有灵性的动物
They're Matagots. They're spirit familiars.
他们守卫着魔法部
They guard the Ministry.
但是他们不会伤害你
But they won't hurt you...
-除非你先攻击他们   -太笨了
- unless you attack them. - Stupefy!
莉塔
- Leta! - Reverte!
Accio!
Ascendio!
好吧  等等
Okay. Wait.
好了
Come on.
好吧  好吧
All right. All right.
等等
Wait.
后退
Move back!
走开   别挡道
Move! Out of the way!
如果你在找克雷登斯  我也是
If you are looking for Credence, me too.
住手
Stop!
尤瑟夫
Yusuf?
真的是你吗
Is that really you?
我妹妹
My little sister .?
所以  他是你哥哥
So, he's your brother?
我是谁
Who am I?
我不知道
I don't know.
我厌倦了没有名字没有不知道身事的生活了
I'm tired of living with no name and no history.
告诉我我的故事  然后你就可以来个了结了
Just tell me my story-then you can end it.
你的故事就是我们的故事
Your story is our story.
我们的故事
Our story.
不  尤瑟夫
No, Yusuf.
我父亲是马斯塔法卡玛
My father was Mustafa Kama.
纯正的塞内加尔血统  成就斐然
A pure-blood of Sénégalese descent and most accomplished.
我妈妈  劳伦娜
My mother, Laurena,
同样是高贵的一个著名的美人
was equally high-bred-a noted beauty.
他们深爱着对方
They were deeply in love.
他们认识一个很有影响的人  他来自法国一个著名的纯正血统家庭
They knew a man of great influence, from a famous French pure-blood family.
他渴望她
He desired her.
莱斯特兰奇用咒语引诱并诱拐她
Lestrange used the Imperius Curse to seduce and abduct her.
我试图阻止  但他攻击了我
I tried to prevent it but he attacked me.
那是我最后一次见到她
That was the last time I ever saw her.
她死了  生了一个小女孩
She died, giving birth to a little girl.
就是你
You.
她去世的消息使我父亲发疯了
The news of her death drove my father insane.
我父亲奄奄一息的时候还要我寻求报复
With his dying breath, my father charged me to seek revenge.
杀了这个世界上莱斯特兰奇最爱的人
Kill the person Lestrange loves best in the world.
我以为一开始会很容易
I thought at first it would be easy.
他只有一个近亲
He had only one close relative
就是你
You.
但是…
But...
说出来
Say it.
他从来没有爱过你
He never loved you.
她死后不到三个月他就再婚了
He remarried not three months after her death.
他对她的爱不亚于他对你的爱
He loved her no more than he had loved you
但后来
But then...
他的儿子考维斯终于出生了
his son, Corvus, was born at last.
还有那个素未谋面的人
And that man who had never known...
它充满了爱
love was filled with it.
他只关心他的考维斯
All he cared about was little Corvus.
所以..就是这样
So... this is the truth?
我是考维斯莱斯特兰奇
I am Corvus Lestrange?
-是的   -不是
- Yes. - No.
意识到马斯塔法卡玛的儿子发誓要复仇
Realizing that Mustafa Kama's son had sworn revenge,
你父亲想把你藏在我找不到你的地方
your father sought to hide you where I couldn't find you.
所以他把你托付给了他的仆人  他的仆人上了一艘开往美国的船
So he confided you to his servant, who boarded a ship for America.
-他确实把考维斯送到了美国  但是  -他的仆人伊玛杜加德
- He did send Corvus to America, but... - His servant, Irma Dugard,
是个半精灵
was a half-elf...
她的魔法很弱
Her magic was weak and
所以没有留下任何蛛丝马迹
therefore left no trace I could follow,
我刚刚才发现你是怎么逃出来的
I had only just discovered how you had escaped
当我收到我从没想过的消息时
when I received news I never expected.
那艘船在海上沉没了
The ship had gone down at sea.
但你活下来了  不是吗
But you survived, didn't you?
不知怎的  有人把你从水里拉出来了
Somehow, someone had pulled you from the water!
儿子被残忍放逐  女儿带着绝望归来
A son cruelly banished Despair of the daughter.
回归  伟大的复仇者啊  扇动翅膀  从水中而来
Return, great avenger with wings from the water.
绝望的女儿站在那里
There, stands the despairing daughter.
你是从海上回来的有翅膀的渡鸦
You are the winged raven returned from the sea,
但我  我是家族毁灭的复仇者
but I, I am the avenger of my family's ruin.
我很同情你  考维斯
I pity you, Corvus,
但你必须死
but you must die.
考维斯 莱斯特兰奇已经死了  我杀了他
Corvus Lestrange is already dead. I killed him.
Accio.
我父亲有一棵很奇怪的家谱
My father owned a very strange family tree.
它只记录男性
It only recorded the men...
我家里的女人被记作花
The women in my family were recorded as flowers.
很漂亮
Beautiful.
也很孤独
Separate.
我父亲把我送到了美国  跟着考维斯...
My father sent me to America, along Corvus..
伊尔玛要装扮成有两个孙子的祖母
Irma was to pose as a grandmother with two grandchildren...
考维斯一直哭个不停
Corvus never stopped crying.
我从没想过要伤害他
I never wanted to hurt him.
我只想摆脱他
I only wanted to be free of him
就一会儿
Just for a moment.
就那么小会儿
Just a single moment.
他们要我们穿上救生衣
They want us to put on life jackets!
你不是故意的  莉塔
You didn't mean to do it, Leta.
所以这不是你的错
So it wasn't your fault.
哦  纽特
Oh, Newt.
你从没见过你不喜欢的怪物
You never met a monster you couldn't love.
莉塔  你知道克雷登斯是谁吗
Leta, do you know who Credence really is?
你知道吗  当你换他的时候
Did you know, when you swapped him?
不知道
No.
奎妮
Queenie?
他们是纯种的法师
They're pure-bloods.
他们为了玩来杀了我们这样的人
They kill the likes of us for sport!
-奎妮   -雅各布
- Quennie. - Jacob.
宝贝  你来了
Honey, you're here! Hi!
嗨  亲爱的  不要这样
Hi, dear, do not.
哦  亲爱的  我很抱歉
Oh, honey, I'm so sorry,
我不该这么做的  我太爱你了
I never should have done it, I love you so much.
-你也知道我爱你  对吧   -是的
- And you know that I love you, right? - Yeah.
-很好  现在让我们离开这里吧   -噢  等等  等等
- Good, now let's get the hell out of here. - Oh, wait. Wait a second.
我只是想也许我们能先听听他到底要说什么
I just thought maybe we could hear him first.
只是听听  就这样
You know, just listen, that's all.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
这是个陷阱
It's a trap.
是啊
Yeah.
奎妮  那棵家谱  全是诱饵
Queenie-the family tree-it's all been bait.
我们得想办法离开这里  马上
We have to find a way out of here, right now
你去找其他人
You go find the others.
你要怎么做
What are you gonna do?
我想想办法
I'll think of something.
我的兄弟们  我的姐妹们  我的朋友们
My brothers, my sisters, my friends:
你们的掌声不是给我的
the great gift of your applause is not for me...
是给你自己的
No. It is for yourselves.
你们今天来是因为渴望
You came today because of a craving
以及想了解更多
and a knowledge
旧的方式不再适合我们
that the old ways serve us no longer.
你今天来是因为你渴望新的东西
You come today because you crave something new.
一些不同的东西
Something different.
据说我讨厌麻鸡
It is said that I hate Les Non-Magiques,
麻瓜
The Muggle.
麻鸡
The No-Maj.
施不了咒的人
The Can't-Spells.
我不恨他们  我一点也不恨
I do not hate them. I do not.
因为我不为仇恨而战
For I do not fight out of hatred.
我说麻瓜不是少数群体
I say the Muggles are not lesser, but other.
不是毫无价值  而是有其他价值
Not worthless, but of other value.
不能任意处理他们
Not disposable,
但却应该被区别对待
but of a different disposition.
魔法的绽放
Magic blooms
只有在稀有的灵魂里才行
only in rare souls.
哦  为了全人类  我们能创造一个怎样的世界
Oh, and what a world we could make, for all of humanity...
我们这些为自由而活的人
We who live for freedom,
为了真相
for truth.
为了爱
And for love.
他们在这里进行非法集会
It isn't illegal to listen to him!
尽量不要使用武力
Use minimum of force on the crowd.
我们不能像他说的那样
We mustn't be what he says we are!
现在是分享我对未来的展望的时候了
The moment has come to share my vision of the future.
如果我们不起义
That awaits if we do not rise up
占据我们在世界上应有的位置
and take our rightful place in the world.
不要在开战了
Not another war.
这就是我们要起义的理由
That is what we are fighting!
那是我们的敌人
That is the enemy.
他们傲慢
Their arrogance.
他们渴望权力
Their power lust.
他们野蛮
Their barbarity.
用不了多久 他们就会把矛头指向我们
How long will it take before they turn their weapons on us?
当我说到这个的时候什么也不要做
Do nothing when I speak of this.
你必须保持冷静
You must remain calm
控制你的情绪
and contain your emotions.
我们中间有傲罗
There are Aurors here among us.
走近点  法师兄弟   加入我们
Come closer, brother wizards! Join us.
什么都别做
Do nothing.
不要用武力
No force.
他们杀了我的很多追随者
They have killed many of my followers.
这是真的
It is true.
他们把我关在纽约折磨我
They confined me tortured me in New York.
他们扼杀了他们的法师同伴
They had struck down their fellow witches and wizards...
只是因为他简单的去寻求真理
For the simple crime of seeking the truth.
因为我想要自由
For wanting freedom...
你的愤怒  有报复的欲望是很自然的
Your anger, your desire for revenge is natural.
不
No!
带这位年轻的战士回到她的家人身边
Take this young warrior back to her family.
消失吧  离开这里  从这里出发
Disapparate. Leave. Go forth from
把这里发生的事情散布出去吧
this place and spread the word.
我们没有使用任何暴力
It is not we who are violent.
傲罗  穿过火焰 加入我的圈子
Aurors, join me in this circle.
向我保证你永远对我忠诚
Pledge to me your eternal allegiance.
要么就去死
Or die.
只有在这里你才会知道什么是自由
Only here shall you know freedom.
只有在这里你才能了解你自己
Only here shall you know yourself.
循规蹈矩
Play by the rules.
孩子们  不要作弊
No cheating, children.
他知道我是谁
He knows who I am.
他只是的知道你的出身  但不知道你的为人
He knows what you were born, not who you are...
克雷登斯
Credence!
奎妮  你得醒醒
Queenie. You gotta wake up!
雅各布  他就是答案
Jacob, he's the answer.
-他的想法就是我们一直想要的   -不  不  不
- He wants what we wants. - No, no, no.
为什么
Why?
这一切都是为了你  克雷登斯
This has all been for you, Credence.
和我一起走
Walk with me.
宝贝  不
Honey, no!
和我一起走
Walk with me!
你疯了
You're crazy.
不
Not!
不   奎妮  别这样
No! Queenie, don't do it!
奎妮
Queenie!
斯卡曼德先生
Mr. Scamander.
你认为邓布利多会为你哀悼吗
Do you think Dumbledore will mourn for you?
格林德沃   住手
Grindelwald! Stop!
莉塔…
Leta...
我想我知道这个
This one I believe I know.
莉塔·莱斯特兰奇
Leta Lestrange.
受到所有法师的鄙视
Despised entirely amongst wizards.
不被爱  被歧视
Unloved, mistreated...
但很勇敢
yet brave.
太勇敢了
So very brave.
回家的时间到了
Time to come home.
我爱你
I love you.
走吧
Go!
我讨厌巴黎
I hate Paris.
大家一起   我们组成一个圆圈  把你的法杖插到地上
Together! In a circle, your wand into the earth.
否则整个巴黎都会消失的
Or all Paris will be lost!
Finite!
我选择了我的一边
I've chosen my side.
哦  过来  找到你了  找到你了
Oh come here. I've got you. I've got you.
我觉得最好还是让他们单独谈谈吧
I think it's best if he speaks to him alone.
他还害怕我吗
Is he frightened of me still?
你得小心点
You need to be careful ..
他不确定他做的选择是否正确
He's not sure he made the right choice.
对他要非常温柔
Be very gentle with him.
我有礼物给你  我的孩子
I have a gift for you, my boy.
莉塔的事是真的吗
Is it true about Leta?
是的
Yes.
我很遗憾
I'm so sorry.
这是个血盟  对吧
It's a blood pact, isn't it?
你们发过誓不对抗彼此的
You swore not to fight each other.
以梅林的名义你是怎么搞到的
How in the name of Merlin did you manage to get?
格林德沃似乎不理解他认为简单的事物的本质
Grindelwald doesn't seem to understand the nature of things he considers simple...
你能毁了它吗
Can you destroy it?
也许吧
Maybe.
你想喝杯茶吗
Would he like a cup of tea?
它想要喝点牛奶
He'll have some milk.
记得把茶匙藏起来
Hide the teaspoons.
你遭受了你的亲人
You have suffered the most heinous of betrayals,
故意给你的最十恶不赦的背叛
most purposely bestowed upon you by your
有自己的血  你自己的血肉
own blood. Your own flesh and blood.
就像他庆祝你的痛苦一样
And just as he has celebrated your torment,
你的兄弟想毁了你
your brother seeks to destroy you.
你家里有个传说  凤凰会来到任何一个家族成员
There is a legend in your family that a phoenix will come to any member
最需要的它地方
who is in dire need.
这是你与生俱来的权利  我的孩子
It is your birthright, my boy.
比如
As is
我现在恢复给你的名字
the name I now restore to you.
奥雷留斯
Aurelius.
奥雷留斯·邓布利多
Aurelius Dumbledore.
当我们重建这个世界的时候  我们将一起载入史册
We will go down in history together as we remake this world.